hello friends it's ben with the third
привет, друзья, это Бен с третьим
episode of everscale news the most
выпуском новостей everscale самые
important news of the ecosystem in two
важные новости экосистемы за две
minutes the teams at everscale are
минуты команды everscale выпускают
pushing one update after another and we
одно обновление за другим, и у
have a lot of intriguing things to tell
нас есть много интересного, о чем мы можем рассказать
you about so let's get started roxas has
вам, так что давайте начнем, roxas
renamed all of its products tonbridge is
переименовал  все его продукты tonbridge
now officially called octus bridge tun
теперь официально называется octus bridge tun
swap has been renamed to flat cube and w
swap был переименован в flat cube, а w
ton was renamed to w ever after
ton был переименован в w после
migration to the new token standard each
перехода на новый стандарт токенов каждый
product will get its own chat for
продукт получит свой собственный чат для
discussions speaking of the new 3.1
обсуждения нового
token standard the migration of all
стандарта токенов 3.1.  миграция всех
infrastructure products has been
инфраструктурных продуктов
completed users can already withdraw
завершена пользователи уже могут вывести
their tokens from the old pawns on tun
свои токены из старых пешек на tun
swap and move them over to flat cube
swap и переместить их в плоский куб
i've done mine already they'll be
я уже сделал мой они будут
converted automatically to the new
автоматически преобразованы в новый
standard after connecting the wallet to
стандарт после подключения кошелька к
the new decks during the recent
новые колоды во время недавней
community meetup some new details about
встречи с сообществом были раскрыты некоторые новые подробности
the roadmap were revealed first of all
о дорожной карте, прежде всего,
flex an advanced decentralized order
сгибание расширенного децентрализованного
book exchange is probably going to be
ордера  k exchange, вероятно, будет
released sooner than stated on the
выпущен раньше, чем указано в
roadmap its development is going very
дорожной карте, его разработка идет
fast and the ever x team feel pretty
очень быстро, и команда ever x
damn confident about it only one or two
чертовски уверена в этом, только один или два
dexes can be compared to flex in terms
dex могут сравниться с flex с точки
of speed and fees and so everscale will
зрения скорости, сборов и так далее.
get one more advantage over the other
получит еще одно преимущество перед другими
blockchains out there in addition to the
блокчейнами в дополнение к
previously mentioned cardano and tesos
ранее упомянутым мостам Cardano и tesos;
bridges everscale will get avalanche
everscale получит мосты avalanche
tron and solana bridges these are going
tron и solan
cross-chain dapps gosh gosh the
;  черт возьми,
decentralized github is also in
децентрализованный github также находится в
development the demo of the product will
разработке, демонстрация продукта
be shown in may gosh will allow
будет показана в мае, черт возьми, это позволит
developers to keep their code on chain
разработчикам хранить свой код в цепочке
instead of relying on centralized
вместо того, чтобы полагаться на централизованные
solutions everscale startup competition
решения.
marketplaces defy and social tools the
defy и социальные инструменты,
top three projects were convo space a
три лучших проекта были convo space, кроссчейн,
cross-chain social app dream base a
социальное приложение, база мечты
platform for musicians and reuters from
платформа для музыкантов и рейтеров из
africa allowing them to mint any writing
Африки, позволяющая им чеканить любое письмо
as an nft and demeter an nft charity
как nft и деметрировать
auction platform that's all for today
платформу благотворительного аукциона nft, на сегодня это все,
stay tuned
следите за обновлениями